嘿
Hey.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
我想知道
Listen, uh...
你们觉得我追得到吉宁吗
do you guys think I have a chance with Janine?
我们讨论过这件事了
Honey, we have been through this before!
对啊  别折磨自己了
Yeah. Don't do this to yourself.
她已经明确表示不可能了
She’s made it pretty clear, it is not going to happen.
那我刚刚吻了她
All right, then. I guess I shouldn't get too excited about the fact...
也不该太兴奋了
...that I just kissed her!
真的假的啊  太好了
Are you serious? That's great!
还得观察
Yeah, well, we'll see.
你吻了她
You kissed her?
吻得相当火热了
Oh, we kissed it up real nice.
你吻了她  然后呢
So you kissed her, What happened after that?
我就跑来告诉你们
I came over here to tell you guys.
而她在对面等你
So she's just waiting over there for ya?
对
Yeah.
老友记  第六季  第11集  见色不忘友
Friends  S06E11  The One With The Apothecary Table
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
（中央咖啡厅）
我得走了  好
I gotta go. Okay
我上舞蹈课要迟到了
I'm gonna be really late for dance class!
好
0Kay.
我真的已经迟到了  好
Okay, now I'm really leaving. Okay, I'm all right.
但你可以
But can you just...
把嘴唇留下来吗
...just leave your lips?
再见  再见
Bye. Bye.
你们吻过她吗
Have you kissed her yet?
相当销魂的
It's awesome!
我怎么吻都吻不够
I could do it forever.
她的吻功比我妈的厨艺还强
You know what? She kisses better than my mom cooks.
幸好你说的是厨艺  对吧
I'm so glad you said "cooks." Right?
瑞秋  你得通知邮局你搬家了
Oh hey Rachel, sweetheart? you've got to tell the post office that you've moved.
你的信件还是都寄到这里来
Okay? We are still getting all your bills and stuff.
陶瓷货仓  剩下的可以扔了
Oh! Oh! Pottery Barn! You can throw the rest away.
我不是你的清洁工
I'm not your garbage man.
我是你的邮差
I'm your mailman.
摩妮卡  你看
Monica, look! Look-look-look!
这里有我订的桌子
Here is that table that I ordered. Ah!
你是在陶瓷货仓买的  对  这叫药师桌
You got it from Pottery Barn? Yeah. It's an apothecary table.
有谁知道药师是什么吗
Does anyone even know what an apothecary is?
就是药剂师
A pharmacist.
瑞秋  菲比最讨厌陶瓷货仓了
Rach, Phoebe hates Pottery Barn.
我也讨厌陶瓷货仓
I hate Pottery Barn too.
我才在床上坐坐  就被赶了出去
They kicked me out just because I sat on a bed.
你脱了裤子钻进被子里了
You took off your pants and got under the sheets.
我很困啊
I was tired.
菲比讨厌陶瓷货仓
Phoebe hates Pottery Barn?
对啊  量产的东西她都讨厌
Yeah, she hates all mass produced stuff.
她觉得她的家俱  应该要有历史  要有典故
She thinks her furniture should have a history, a story behind it.
这有典故啊
Well this has a story behind it.
这是大老远从白原店运来的
I mean they had to ship it all the way from the White Plains store.
她喜欢独一无二
It’s gotta be one of a kind.
就像她那个丑到爆的水果陶碗
Y'know like umm, y'know uh, what's that God awful ceramic fruit bowl she has on her counter?
那是我做的
Hey! I made that for her.
你会捏陶   对
You made pottery? Yeah.
是从垃圾堆捡来的啦
I made it out of a fruit bowl I found in the garbage.
你把桌子搬回家  肯定会被念到死
I'm telling -- If you put that in her apartment, you'll never hear the end of it.
好  我就说那是古董
Okay fine! I'll-I'll just tell her that it's an antique apothecary table.
她也不必知道它的出处
She doesn't have to know where it came from.
你看  我爱死这些小抽屉了
Ah, I love these drawers.
上面说可以放三百张CD
Oh, look! It says that it holds 300 CDs.
正如往昔的药师桌
Ah, just like the apothecary tables of yore.
然后农夫说
So the farmer says:
"那不是母牛  你也不是在挤奶"
"That's not a cow, and you're not milking."
你们能在一起真好
I am so glad you guys got together,
钱德跟我一直在找一对情侣朋友  现在总算找到了
Chandler and I are always looking for a couple to go out with and now we have one.
我们是成双又成对
We're a couple of couples.
今晚真开心   那家餐厅好棒
I had so much fun tonight. What a great restaurant!
钱德  我居然让你请客
And Chandler, I can't believe I let you pay for this one.
再次感谢
Thanks again, man.
明天要不要过来  我来做我说的那种意大利面
So do you guys gonna come over tomorrow? I'll make that pasta thing I was telling you about.
那太好了
That'd be great! Okay.
不过至少让我们带酒来
Oh, but hey look, at least let us bring the wine.
不必客气了  不行  我坚持
Joey, you don't have too! Ah, I insist.
你会买吧   会啦
You'll get the wine, right? Yeah.
那就晚安  明天见
Okay, good night. See you tomorrow.
好期待喔
Can't wait.
我们要怎么逃过一劫
How are we going to get out of that one?
什么  我没办法连续应酬他们
What? I can't handle two nights in a row...
两晚
...with them.
摩妮卡和钱德有什么不好
What-what’s wrong with Monica and Chandler?
不晓得  他们就是有点
I don’t know, they're just a little...
哈啦
...blah!
Blah?
他很哈啦  她
Well, you know, he's blah. She's just...
她很娇小  嗓门却很大
She's very loud for such a small person.
他们是我最要好的朋友
Uh, they're my best friends.
我们不能跟他们往来吗  那可就麻烦了
Are you saying we can't hang out with them? 'Cause that'd be a problem.
不是  往来当然可以
No! Of course we can still hang out with them.
只是不要连续两晚
Just y'know, not two nights in a row.
好吗  好吧
Okay? I guess.
谢谢
Thank you.
要我卖了朋友  给你买礼物都行
If you want, I'll sell my friends and use the money to buy you presents.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
好棒的桌子  在哪里买的
Ooh! What a great table! Where did you get it?
你猜
Guess.
跳蚤市场
Um, a flea market?
我就知道你会一猜即中
Ha, See, I knew, I knew you would get it on the first guess.
很酷吧   这是药师桌
Isn't it cool? It's an apothecary table.
哇哦
Wow!
你可以想像  他们就是把药材
Oh you can just imagine that this is where...
存放在这里面
...they kept all their stuff to make potions.
你知道  对啊
You know? Ooh, yes.
几乎能闻到鸦片的味道
Ooh, you can almost smell the opium.
就是啊
Almost.
多少钱
Oh, how much was it?
才5百
Just only 500 bucks.
跳蚤市场买的要5百
500 bucks at a flea market?
我以为你是问
Oh, okay see I thought,I thought you meant how much was it...
当年  全新时候的价钱
...when it was new, y'know like back then
不是  就是说嘛
Oh, no. Yeah, no.
因为是跳蚤市场   所以差不多1块钱
I mean it was at a flea market, so it was y'know, it was like a dollar.
1块钱  再加50元
A dollar? And fifty?
总共51元
So it was like one and fifty dollars.
他们用古法算钱  对
Ohh, okay, they gave you the old-time pricing. Yeah.
这是哪个年代的
Well, what period is it from?
往昔年代
Uh, it's from yore.
就是 "往昔的时代"  知道吗
Like, the "days of yore," you know?
对  我知道
Yes, I do.
天哪  真是太完美了
It's just perfect. Oh, good.
这一定有很棒的典故
Wow! I bet it has a great story behind it too.
卖方有提到它的出处或者
Did they tell you anything? Like y’know where it was from or...
有  这个我知道  它来自白原
Yes, that I know. This is from, uh, White Plains.
白原
White Plains. Mm-hm.
听起来好神奇的一个地方
Ooh, it sounds like such a magical place.
我来了
Hey! I'm here. Hi!
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
你喜欢吗   完了
You like it? Oh, my God!
这是我的新药师桌
It's my new apothecary table!
罗斯  菲比就快到了  不能让她看到
Ross! Phoebe'll be here any second. She can't see this.
为什么  她一定会喜欢  这是好东西
Well why not?! She'll love it. It's the real thing.
是在陶瓷货仓买的
I got it at Pottery Barn.
我知道  我也买了一张
I know you did! I bought the same one.
她看到你的桌子  就会知道我骗她
And if she sees your table she's gonna know that I lied to her.
我说我们的是原版  为什么
I told her ours was an original. Why did you do that?
因为她讨厌陶瓷货仓
Because she hates Pottery Barn.
她讨厌陶瓷货仓
She hates Pottery Barn?
我也很惊讶  她说那是量产
I know! I know, She says it's all mass-produced...
没有真品  大家买的都一样
...nothing is authentic, and everyone winds up having the same stuff.
她随时都会进来  拿个东西先盖住  好吗
So come on! she's gonna be here any second! Can we please just cover this up with something?! Please?
什么  不  不要
What? No, no.
我才不要遮遮掩掩的
I am not gonna hide it from Phoebe.
不过我也买了很漂亮的床单
Although I did get some great Pottery Barn sheets.
我忘了他们也出床单
Ooh, I forgot they made sheets!
废话
Heh, yeah.
她居然会讨厌陶瓷货仓
I still can't believe she hates Pottery Barn.
罗斯  别再念了  她又不是讨厌你
Ross, get over it! It's not like she hates you.
但是  她讨厌陶瓷货仓嘛
Yeah, but Pottery Barn?
我觉得  她根本就是怪胎
You know what I think? It's just she-she's weird.
因为她是双胞胎  双胞胎都很怪
Y’know it’s because she's a twin. Twins are weird.
罗斯  她不是怪胎  她只是希望她的东西独一无二
Ross, she's not weird. She just wants her stuff to be one-of-a-kind.
什么才是最不独一无二的  双胞胎
Huh. You know what's not one-of-a-kind? A twin!
菲比来了  把灯关掉  看电影吧
Ooh, Phoebe's here! Okay, let's turn out the lights and watch the movie.
好漂亮的床单  喜欢是吧
Okay. Hey, ooh, cool sheet! You like it?
想知道哪里买的吗  好啊
You want to know where I got it? Sure.
在跳蚤市场买的
At a flea market.
你去跳蚤市场买床单
You buy your sheets at a flea market?
罗斯  别这么小气吧
Ross come on, you gotta loosen the purse strings a little.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
晚餐再过20分钟就好了  好兴奋喔
The dinner will be ready in 20 minutes. This is so exciting.
这是你今晚要带过来的酒
And here is the bottle of wine for you to bring over tonight.
你想送花给摩妮卡
You were also gonna buy Monica flowers...
却买不起  因为你付了昨晚晚餐的钱
...but you couldn't afford it,because you paid for dinner last night.
谢谢  但今晚只有我要过去
Thanks. But, uh, it's just gonna be me tonight.
吉宁怎么了  她病得很重
What happened to Janine? She's, uh, really sick.
真糟糕  对啊  她整天都在房里
That's too bad. Yeah, she's been in there all day.
发高烧  鼻塞
Uh, high fever, nose problem. It's...
痰痰痰痰痰
Phlegm, phlegm, phlegm, phlegm, phlegm.
摩妮卡   钱德
Monica! Chandler!
今晚真抱歉  乔伊说了吗
I'm really-really sorry about tonight. I don't know if Joey told you...
有出戏我一定得去看  抱歉
...I just couldn't get out of going to this play. I'm sorry.
玩得开心点  好
Have a great time, huh?
怪了  没有痰啊
That's funny, I saw no phlegm.
不  她真的病得很重
Oh, no, she really is sick.
那她为什么要去看戏
Then why is she going to a play?
你知道的  感冒想退烧
Uh, well, you know, "Starve a fever...
就要去看戏
...go to a play for a cold."
乔伊   吉宁为什么不来吃饭
Joey! Why is Janine not coming over for dinner?
她不想连续两晚都陪你们
Uh, she didn't want to hang out with you guys two nights in a row.
对不起
I'm so sorry.
她为什么不想陪我们
Why doesn't she want to hang out with us?
因为她觉得  你很哈啦
Because she, uh, she-she thinks that you are "blah."
而摩妮卡  你的嗓门太大
And that, uh, you, Monica, are too loud.
什么
What?!
What?
所以她昨晚只是假装开心
So she was just pretending to have a good time last night?
她当面骗我们
She was lying to our faces?
太扯了
I can't believe this.
她凭什么批评我们
Who is she to judge us?
我们对她多好  我才不是哈啦  我是谈笑风生
We couldn't have been nicer to her. And I am not "blah." I am a hoot!
我知道  我知道
I know, I know.
拜托啦  别生气
Come on, please, you guys. Don't be mad.
她一定是
I'm sure she just, she just said that stuff ...
紧张才会这么说  你们是我最好的朋友
because she was nervous and you guys are like my best friends!
我们又是第一次约会
Y’know? And it was our first date.
而且  她病得很重
Plus, she's really sick.
你明明说那是假的
No, you sh—No you said you made that up!!
但你不觉得"生病"比"看戏"好吗
I know, but don't you think the "sick" thing is way better than the "play" thing?
都很好  我通常都说  摩妮卡又醉了
Eh, they're both good. I generally just go with, "Monica's drunk again."
拜托啦  再给她一次机会
Come on you guys, please just give her another chance.
她一定会喜欢你们的  我保证  当然好
She'll come around, I promise. Of course we will.
回去煮饭吧  好
Come on, we gotta make dinner. Okay.
我不喜欢那个女人
I do not like that woman!
我听得见
I can hear you!
我的嗓门真的很大
I am loud!
真好笑
Isn't it good?
菲比  别把脚翘在我的新
Hey Pheebs, could you please not put your feet up on my new...
旧床单上
...old sheet.
好
Oh, sure.
我的药师桌
My apothecary table!
什么  不
What? No!
这张桌子是哪里买的  陶瓷货仓  好吗
Ross, where did you get this? I got it at Pottery Barn!! Okay?!
天哪  菲比
Oh, my God! Phoebe,
陶瓷货仓抄袭我们古董的设计
Pottery Barn has ripped off the design of our antique!
天哪  要是他们会抄袭
Wow! Oh my God, well if they've ripped off our table...
那张桌子一定不止值51元
...ours must be worth much more than one and fifty dollars.
这张连鸦片的味道都没有
Well this doesn’t even smell like opium.
当然没有  只有你洒出来的酒味
Of course not, it smells like wine, which you spilled!
谢谢你还毁了我的床单
And thanks for wrecking my sheet by the way.
别激动  罗斯  我赔你80分就是了
Ross, calm down. I'll give you the 80 cents.
再来一次
Okay, one more time.
钱德  你还要柳橙汁吗
Chandler, would you like some more orange juice?
音量刚刚好  就是啊
Perfect decibel. I know!
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
你们在干什么
Uh, what are you guys doing?
没什么  就是聊天哈啦
Nothing. We're just talking. You know, blah-blah-blah.
别这样  你们说过要尽力的
Look, come on you guys, you said you were gonna try!
我来找你们和吉宁一起去看电影
I came over here to invite you guys to a movie with me and Janine.
你们觉得呢  非常乐意
What do you say? I'd like to...
但是  我不确定有时间
...but I'm not sure if we have the time.
真好笑  我也很无奈
Ha, very funny. I don't know what to do.
我真的很希望你们处得来
I really want you guys to get along.
拜托  你们跟我们去吧  这是你们欠我的
Just please, come to the movie with us. I mean you owe me!
我们欠你  没错
We owe you? That's right.
你们刚交往时  我帮了很多忙
I helped you guys out a lot in the start of your relationship.
我还帮你们偷鸡摸狗6个月
I helped you guys sneak around for like six months.
跟白痴一样
I looked like an idiot.
还被羞辱
And I was humiliated.
却只赚了2百
And I only made $200.
我们没有给你钱
We didn't give you any money.
你以为我不知道吗
You don't think I know that?
我不知道该拿它配藤条餐桌椅
see I can't decide whether it would go better next to the new wicker dining chair..
黄色书桌
...the Sahara desk...
还是螺形托脚桌
...or the Parker console table.
原来你们这里也有陶瓷货仓
Wow! I didn't know that there was a Pottery Barn up here.
我知道  我有点买疯了  有点
I know, I know. I went a little crazy. A little?
这里就像目录第72页
Your place looks like page 72 of the catalog.
看
Look at that!
装饰  鸟笼  大号的
The ornamental birdcage! Large. Ha, ha.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
罗斯  小心  那个很老了
Oh, Ross? Be careful. That is very old.
殖民地时代早期的  鸟商  都用那个带 鸟上市场
Okay? Early Colonial bird merchants used to bring their birds to market in that.
有意思
Fascinating.
又一个惊人的发现
Another amazing find! Wow.
它一定也有很棒的典故  没错
Oh I bet this has a great story too. It does.
这是殖民地时期  分隔房间的装置
It is a room-separating apparatus from Colonial times.
有好多东西都来自殖民地时期
Huh, a lot of this stuff is from the Colonial times.
还有哪些时期呢   瑞秋
What are some other time periods, Rachel?
有往昔
Well, there's yore.
还有昨年
Ahem, and, uh, you know, yesteryear.
瑞秋对这种东西真的很有眼光
Yeah no, I'm telling you Rachel has such a good eye for this stuff.
罗斯  如果你家要重新布置
Ross, y'know if you ever decide to redecorate--
我觉得很有必要重新布置
and I think you should--
你应该找瑞秋帮忙
you should ask Rachel to help.
他才不需要我的帮忙
Oh honey, he doesn't need my help.
拜托  他早该扔掉那些  你是怎么说的
Oh, come on! I think he's ready to get rid of the. What'd you call it?
廉价的赝品和恐龙垃圾
The, uh, "cheap knockoffs and dinosaurjunk"?
是吗
Really?
你知道吗  既然你这么清楚我的需求
You know, since you have such a great sense of what I need--
我这里有60元
Uh, here's 60 bucks.
你带着菲比去殖民时期跳蚤市场
Why don't you take Phoebe down to that Colonial, uh, flea market...
帮我办货吧
...and get me some stuff?
我觉得菲比不会想去
Y'know what? I don't, I don't think Phoebe wants to come.
不  我想去  她想去
No! I do want to! She does want to.
她想去  没错
She does want to. Yeah!
菲比  我不知道该说什么  上次跳蚤市场还比较逛得
Pheebs, I don't know what to say.I guess the flea market was just better last time.
至少我帮罗斯买了床单  没错
Well, at least I got these sheets for Ross. Yeah.
看  是陶瓷货仓
Ugh, look at this. Pottery Barn.
你不懂  别看了
Ugh, yeah, you know what? Don't look at it.
真的  别看了  你看
Seriously, don't look at it. No! Look-look!
他们抄袭我们的咖啡桌
There's the coffee table they stole from us.
那些混蛋  我们走
Oh, those bastards! Let's go.
那台电风扇跟我们的有点像  还有那个乌笼和
That fan kind of looks like ours, and the birdcage, and...
等一下  这简直就像是我们的客厅
Wait a second, this is our exact living room!
不  才不像呢
No! No it’s not!
菲比  我们的完全不一样
No it’s not! Come on, Phoebe, ours is totally different.
我们没有   我们没有那盏灯
I mean, we don't have the - We don't have the…that lamp! .
还有那扇屏风  是在另一边
And-and that screen is y'know, on the other side.
天哪  那些都是陶瓷货仓的东西
Oh, my God. This is where you got all our stuff.
陶瓷货仓  我的天哪  不是
Pottery Barn! Oh, my God! No. no.
好啦  你说对了  对不起
Okay-okay look—no I did,, all right? I'm sorry.
我想要这些东西  又知道你讨厌陶瓷货仓
I just wanted this stuff and I know how you feel about Pottery Barn.Just...
你不要生气  但是我气死了  气死了
Come on don't be mad. No-no-no, but I am mad!I am mad!
这代表世间所有丑恶的东西
Because this stuff is everything that is wrong with the world...
都在我的客厅里
And it’s all sitting up in my living room...
而我却只想着我没有那盏灯
...and all I can think about is how I don't have that lamp!
那就买下那盏灯
Well, then, honey, buy the lamp.
我们有罗斯给的60元
We have that 60 bucks from Ross.
不行  不行
I can't! I can't!
除非
Unless...
你是说我不买那盏灯   你就要搬走吗
Well are you saying that-that you would move out if-if I didn't buy that lamp?
不  我不会搬走
No, I'm not gonna move out!
你是说我不买那盏灯  你就要搬走吗
But are you saying that you would move out if I didn't buy that lamp?
没错  我一定会搬走  那我就没办法了
Oh. Yes! I would so move out. Okay then I don't have a choice!
那我就得买那盏灯  没错
I have to buy that lamp! That's right.
不过至少那张药师桌是真货
But at least the apothecary table is real.
真好  大家都很尽兴吧
Well, this-this-this was great. Didn't everybody have a great time?
我很尽兴  真的  我想说
I did. I really did. And you guys, I've got to say...
很抱歉上次聚会后  我态度怪怪的
I'm sorry if I was a little weird after the last time we went out.
可能是紧张吧
I guess I was just nervous or something.
我们完全可以理解  别放在心上
That’s totally understandable. Don't worry about it.
那么我们可以再一起出去了
So we can go out again?
当然可以  当然
Oh yeah! Absolutely.
那就晚安  晚安
Okay, well, good night. Good night.
看吧
See,huh?
很好玩吧
Wasn't that fun?
我们非搬家不可
We have got to move.
什么
What?
我就知道
I knew it!
你的嗓门也不小  死丫头
Y'know, you're not so quiet yourself, missy!
我哈啦  比看现代舞更无聊的
And I'm blah? Listen, The only thing more boring than watching modern dance...
就是听你聊现代舞
...is having to listen to you talk about it.
"钱德
"Oh, Chandler...
我刚才看得浑然忘我"
...I just lost myself in the movement."
我知道你在说话
You know, I know you're talking...
但我只听到  叽哩呱啦叽哩呱啦
...but all I hear is blah-blah-blah-blah-blah.
好  你和我  现在出去  单挑
All right, you and me! Let's go, right now!
好了  好了  够了  够了
All right! All right! Enough! Enough!
够了  你们回去吧  我要跟吉宁谈一谈
Enough! Enough! You two, go home. I gotta talk to Janine.
你绝对可以撂倒她
Y'know I think you can take her.
别让我在走廊上碰到你
You'd better hope I don't see you in the hallway!
好了
All right. Uh...
我们有个小小的问题
we've got a little bit of a problem here.
他们是我的朋友  你不能对他们无礼
These people are my friends; you can't treat them that way.
他们也对我出言不逊   我知道  我会找他们谈
They said stuff to me too. I know, I know! I'll talk to them about it.
他们对我很重要
They mean so much to me.
就像我的家人
They're like my family, you know?
如果你们一见面就吵
If you guys are gonna be fighting all the time...
我们就不可能在一起  这是行不通的
I don't think we can be together.It just, it just can't work,okay?
行不通的
It can't.
我很不开心
I'm very upset.
好  好吧
0Kay. Okay.
要是我过去道歉呢
Would, would it help if I went over and apologized?
好啊
Yeah! Yeah!
那就太好了
That would be very helpful! Yeah.
我说过在走廊上碰到会怎样
What did I tell you about the hall?
我只是要过去向你们道歉
I was just coming over here to apologize for my behavior!
我很希望能跟你们做朋友
I'd really like it if we could be friends.
我知道那样会让乔伊很高兴  所以
Well, I know that would make Joey happy, so...
我也愿意
...I would like that too.
太好了  来吧
Great. Now, come on.
很高兴能达成共识  我也是
Well, I'm glad we worked it out. Me too.
回头见  再见
Okay. I'll see you. Bye.
听都听得见  够了
Or I'll hear you. That's it, big girl.
慢着
Wait!
你最好快逃
You'd better run!
你听见了吗  听见了
Did you hear that? Yeah uh,
我该怎么办  难为你了
What am I gonna do? Yeah, I'm sorry man.
要去看吗  当然
Want to go watch? Yeah!
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
大家好  她搬出去了吗
How you doing? So, uh, did she move out?
差不多了
Pretty much, yeah.
你居然就这样跟她分手了
I cannot believe you broke up with her just like that.
不适合就是不适合
Well, When it's not right, you know it.
你还好吧  死不了
You okay? Yeah! Yeah. I'll be all right.
我有办法让你开心  什么办法
You know what'd cheer you up? What?
我明晚要教侵蚀理论
I'm giving this lecture on erosion theories tomorrow night.
你应该来听听
I think you should come.
你说的对  我确实开心多了
You're right, that did cheer me up.